https://zedomax.com/blog/privacy/

Netflix
NEVER GIVE UP!
Purpose and Scope
This policy discloses what information we gather about you when you visit any of our web sites (all zedomax.com and affiliated network sites) or buy product directly from us. It describes how we use that information and how you can control it.
Information Zedomax Network LLC gathers and tracks
Personal information
We use the personal information you provide voluntarily to send information you’ve requested and to fulfill orders. The specific use of your personal information varies, depending on how you contact us:
We never sell or rent your email address or other personally identifiable information you provide us under these circumstances.
With third parties we retain to perform functions on our behalf, such as fulfilling orders, are restricted from using your information for any other purpose.
We do not rent or sell our email lists.
We release personal information when we believe that release is appropriate to comply with the law, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Zedomax.com, our users, or others. This may include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Aggregated tracking information
We analyze visitors’ use of our sites by tracking information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We also share this anonymous traffic and demographic information in aggregate form with advertisers and other business partners. We do not share any information with advertisers that can identify an individual user.
We use Google, a third party publishing service to monetize our site.  Google collects information for more relevant advertising, you can read their Privacy Policy.
We use Statcounter, a third party web analytics service to improve our web site performance and user experience. We use this information to improve usability on our sites and to help support our customers online needs.  Statcounter does not reveal any personally identifiable information, such as names or email address.
For more information on the Statcounter service and privacy policy, please see their privacy policy.
Cookies
A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser when you visit our sites. Cookies enable our systems to recognize your computer, so that we can provide you with personalized information and features. We also use cookies to track user traffic patterns.
On our sites, we and some of our advertisers use a third-party ad server to display ads. These ads may contain cookies. The ad server receives these cookies, and we don’t have access to them.
You can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies or to block cookies. If you block cookies, you may not be able to use certain site features or functions.
Third Party Cookies
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.
Notification of Changes
This privacy policy was put in effect on June 9th, 2009.
If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on zedomax.com.  If we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users via email. Users will be able to opt out of any new use of their personal information.
How to update, correct, or delete your information
Email: To update or unsubscribe from our email newsletters or product announcements,  send email to sales zedomax.com.
Leave a Reply Cancel reply
Your email address will not be published.Comment Name
Email
Save my name, email, and website in this browser for the next time I comment.
Subscribe to Zedomax.com
Recent Commentsben on Samsung Vibrant, Captivate, Epic 4G, and Fascinate [Galaxy S Driver Download]!matt beilke on DIY Canoe Made out of PVC Pipe & Duct Tape!Mac on Does the Moon Pull the Water From the Ocean?syonxu on HACK – Unlock Windows XP Password without any Programs!supergamerbro on PS3 Hack – PS3 Six axis Controller Can Be Used In Windows!
Top Rated Reviews
TokyoFlash LED Watch Changing Lanes Review!
Android Tablet Prototype Review!
Top 10 Best DSLR Lenses Review!
Best Earbud Reviews
Best Receipt Scanner Review
Best DSLR Laptop Backpack Review
Best Portable HD Camcorder Review
Manual Treadmill Review!
Top DIY Projects
Top 10 Best Star Wars DIY Projects!
Top 10 GMail HOWTOs!
Top 10 Coffee HOWTOs!
Top 10 DIY Digital Frame HOWTOs!
Top 30 LED Projects
Top 10 LCD/LED Watches
Top 10 Digital LED Watches
Top 10 Ways to Recycle Boxes!
Top 10 3D Accessory DIY/HOWTOs!
Top 10 DIY Digital Frame HOWTOs!
Top Smartphone HOWTOs
How to Install Ubuntu on Android smartphones!
Top 10 Best iPod/iPhone DIY Speakers!
Top 10 Best iPhone Mods/Hacks!
Top 10 Best Nexus One Hacks!
Top 10 Homemade DIY iPhone Docks!
Top 10 DIY iPhone/iPod Touch Cases
Top Computer HOWTOs
How to Install SSD on your Laptop!
How to Crack WEP!
How to Install Windows 7 with a USB Flash Drive!
Mac Hacks - Top 10 Ways to Run Mac on PC!
Mac Hacks - Snow Leopard's Hidden Features!
World's Most Awesome DIY PC Case Mods
Top 10 HOWTOs for faster Ubuntu Linux!
Top 10 Arduino DIY Projects!
Top Photography/Photoshop DIYs
Canon EOS 7D Essentials Review
Top 10 Best Camera DIY HowTos!
Top 10 Fat-to-Thin Photoshop HOWTOs
Top 10 Best Lomo Action HOWTOs!
Top Food HOWTOs/Recipes
How to Make Beef Sisig!
How to Make Restaurant Style Thai Hot Sauce!
How to Make Thai Pork and Shrimp Salad!
How to Make Thai Coconut Soup!
How to Make Great Homemade Pizza!
zedomax.com
Copyright © 2010 by zedomax.com - Zedomax - The DIY, HOWTO, Mod, Hacks, Gadgets, and Tech Blog! - Privacy
